export const htmlQuestions=[
    {question:"What is the best way to apply bold styling to text?", 
    0:"<strong>", 
    1:"<bold>", 
    2:"<b>", 
    3:"font-weight:bold;", 
    correct:0
    },
    {question:"How do you confirm that a document is written in HTML5?", 
    0:"The server wraps the webpage in an HTML5 wrapper.", 
    1:"Use the <!DOCTYPE html> declaration that starts the document.", 
    2:"The browser receives encoding from the server to display the document with HTML5.", 
    3:"It is enclosed in a <html> tag.", 
    correct:1
    },
    {
    question: "What is HTML?",
    0:"Programming language",
    1:"Language used for styling text",
    2:"Server-side language",
    3:"Hyper Text Markup Language",
    correct:3
    },
    {
    question:"Choose the biggest heading",
    0:"<strong>",
    1:"<h6>",
    2:"<h1>",
    3:"<heading>",
    correct:2    
    },
    {
    question:"Which element is inline?",
    0:"<img>",
    1:"<input>",
    2:"<div>",
    3:"<form>",
    correct:1   
    },
    {
    question:"Which is the correct hyperlink?",
    0:"<a>www.foo.pl</a>",
    1:"<a href=\"www.foo.pl\">foo</a>",
    2:"<a src=\"www.foo.pl\">foo</a>",
    3:"<a href=\"www.foo.pl\" value=\"foo\">",
    correct:1    
    },
    {
    question:"Which elements are inside <table></table>?",
    0:"<thead>,<ttable>,<tfoot>",
    1:"<tr>,<tablecaption>,<hr>",
    2:"<tr>,<td>,<th>",
    3:"<tbody>,<tfoot>,<tcontent>",
    correct:2    
    },
    {
    question:"Which tag is used for numbered list?",
    0:"<ol>",
    1:"<ul>",
    2:"<li>",
    3:"<caption>",
    correct:0    
    },
    {
    question:"What is the <hr> tag typically used for?",
    0:"This tag is depreciated and should not be used.",
    1:"It draws a horizontal line.",
    2:"It designates a shift of topic at the section level.",
    3:"It designates a topic shift within a section at the paragraph level.",
    correct:3    
    },
    {
    question:"To get a link to open in a new window or tab, use the __ attribute.",
    0:"open",
    1:"newtab",
    2:"_new",
    3:"_blank",
    correct:3    
    },
    //10 questions line  
    { 
    question:"The __ tag is used for marking up a short code snippet and the __ tag is used for marking up a longer block of code.",
    0:"<span>, <code>",
    1:"<code>, <pre>",
    2:"<div>, <span>",
    3:"<mark>, <span>",
    correct:1    
    },
    {
    question:"What is the difference between <input type=\"submit\" value=\"click me\"> and <button type=\"submit\">Click me</button>?",
    0:"There is no difference. Both will render a button that submits a form.",
    1:"Both will submit a form. However, the <input> can have content other than text, like an image or nested HTML elements, while the <button> cannot.",
    2:" Both will submit a form. However, the <button> can have content other than text, like an image or nested HTML elements, while the <input> cannot.",
    3:"<input type=\"button\"> has been deprecated in HTML5. You should use the <button> tag instead.",
    correct:2    
    },
    {
    question:"Which HTML attribute specifies an alternate text for an image, if the image cannot be displayed?",
    0:"alt",
    1:"src",
    2:"title",
    3:"alternative",
    correct:0    
    },
    {
    question:"Which doctype is correct for HTML5?",
    0:"doctype is not needed in HTML5 anymore",
    1:"<!DOCTYPE HTML5>",
    2:`<!DOCTYPE HTML PUBLIC "-//W3C//DTD HTML 5.0//EN" "http://www.w3.org/TR/html5/strict.dtd">`,
    3:"<!DOCTYPE html>",
    correct:3     
    },
    {
    question:"What is the correct HTML element for playing video files?",
    0:"<media>",
    1:"<video>",
    2:"<movie>",
    3:"<mp4>",
    correct:1     
    },
    {
    question:"In HTML, which attribute is used to specify that an input field must be filled out?",
    0:"formvalidate",
    1:"placeholder",
    2:"validate",
    3:"required",
    correct:3     
    },
    {
    question:"Which input type defines a slider control?",
    0:"slider",
    1:"range",
    2:"controls",
    3:"slide",
    correct:1     
    },
    {
    question:"What is the best semantic way to indicate that text refers to keyboard entry?",
    0:"<p>Press the <tt>Enter</tt> key to proceed.</p>",
    1:"<p>Press the <kbd>Enter</kbd> key to proceed.</p>",
    2:"<p>Press the <samp>Enter</samp> key to proceed.</p>",
    3:"<p>Press the Enter key to proceed.</p>",
    correct:1     
    },
    {
    question:" Which tag is the root element of an HTML document?",
    0:"<root>",
    1:"<html>",
    2:"<head>",
    3:"<DOCTYPE html>",
    correct:1     
    },
    {
    question:"What does this code do? <audio controls src=\"sound.mp3\" type=\"audio/mpeg\">When does this text display?</audio>",
    0:"The text displays when the browser cannot play the sound.",
    1:"The text displays over the audio controls, unless CSS is used to position it elsewhere.",
    2:"The text displays under the audio controls.",
    3:"The text never displays.",
    correct:0     
    },
    {
    question:"Which image formats can be displayed by all web browsers?",
    0:"JPG, GIF, TIF",
    1:"TIF, BMP, GIF",
    2:"JPG, TIF, BMP",
    3:"PNG, GIF, JPG",
    correct:3     
    },
    {
    question:"How to add style.css file inside head element?",
    0:"<link style=\"style.css\">",
    1:"<style src=\"style.css\"></style>",
    2:"<link rel=\"stylesheet\" href=\"style.css\">",
    3:"<style link=\"style.css\"",
    correct:2     
    },
    {
    question:"What is the correct way to describe an empty element?",
    0:"It display nothing on a website.",
    1:"It has child content but no closing tag.",
    2:"It has opening and closing tags but no child content.",
    3:"It has no child content and no closing tag.",
    correct:3     
    },
    // {
    // question:"",
    // 0:"",
    // 1:"",
    // 2:"",
    // 3:"",
    // correct:     
    // },
    
];